It's just a bunch of Hocus Pocus.
Hocus Pocus is a fantasy, comedy, family film directed by Kenny Ortega.
After 300 years of slumber, three sister witches are accidentally resurrected in Salem on Halloween night, and it is up to
three kids and their newfound feline friend to put an end to the witches' reign of terror once and for all.
Winifred Sanderson, played by Bette Midler.
Sarah Sanderson, played by Sarah Jessica Parker.
Mary Sanderson, played by Kathy Najimy.
Max Dennison, played by Omri Katz.
Dani Dennison, played by Thora Birch.
Allison, played by Vinessa Shaw.
Hocus Pocus is a 1993 American fantasy comedy film directed by Kenny Ortega from a screenplay
by Mick Garris and Neil Cuthbert, and a story by David Kirschner and Garris.
It follows a villainous comedic trio of witches (Bette Midler, Sarah Jessica Parker, and Kathy Najimy) who are
inadvertently resurrected by a teenage boy (Omri Katz) in Salem, Massachusetts, on Halloween night.
The film was released in North America on July
16, 1993, by Walt Disney Pictures.
Upon its original release, it received mixed reviews from critics and was initially a
box-office bomb, possibly losing Disney around $16.5 million during its theatrical run.
However, largely through many annual airings on Disney Channel and Freeform (formerly ABC Family, Fox Family and The Family Channel) all throughout the month
of October, Hocus Pocus has been rediscovered by audiences, resulting in a yearly spike in home media sales of the film every Halloween season.
The annual celebration of Halloween has helped make the film a cult classic.
The film spawned a franchise, consisting of a sequel novelization, a
theme park attraction, a TV special, and even a short film.
A sequel, Hocus Pocus 2, written by Jen D'Angelo and directed by Anne Fletcher, was released
on September 30, 2022, on Disney+, with a third film currently in development.
The film explores themes of witch, virgin, sibling
relationship, magic, halloween.
The tone is lighthearted.